<?xml version="1.0"  encoding="utf-8"?>
<window id="" title="" left="0" top="0" width="600" height="288" center="" style="2248146944" style_ex="0" titleHeight="0" icon="" logo="" frame=""  frameCorner="10,10,10,10" drawSimple = "1" roundcorner="0">
 <static id="id_static_tip2" title="Users of this software, if you do not accept these terms, please do not use the services provided by the platform; once you use them, it indicates that you have agreed to the following terms. If you violate the following terms, this software has the right to ban you from entering this software without your knowledge, or take legal measures.
1. The information content and data published or generated by the user on this software are jointly owned by the user and this software. No other organization or individual may copy, reproduce or modify the content without the authorization and consent of the user and this software. If reproduced Please indicate the source. Users are not allowed to publish information containing the following content on this software:
1) Violates the basic principles stipulated in the national constitution;
2) Endangering national security, leaking state secrets, subverting state power, and undermining national unity;
3) Damaging national honor and interests;
4) Inciting ethnic hatred, ethnic discrimination, and undermining ethnic unity;
5) Undermining national religious policies and promoting cults and feudal superstitions;
6) Spread rumors, disrupt social order, and undermine social stability;
7) Spread obscenity, pornography, gambling, violence, murder, terror or instigate crime;
8) Insulting or defaming others and infringing upon others' legitimate rights and interests;
9) Contains other content prohibited by laws and administrative regulations;
10) For other content that this software deems inappropriate to publish here, this software reserves the right to delete and change the above-mentioned relevant information. Any losses caused to users shall be borne by the users themselves.
2. Users should ensure that they provide true registration information, ensure that the information is correct and complete, and update relevant content in a timely manner when user-related information changes. This software does not assume any liability for losses when any losses are caused due to untrue information.
3. Users are advised to keep their account information safe. Once the account information is lost or leaked, this software will not bear any liability for losses.
4. This software cannot guarantee that the services provided can meet all user requirements, nor can it guarantee whether existing services will be interrupted during use, nor can it guarantee the timeliness, security, and accuracy of the services.
5. If the user causes losses to the software or any third party due to violation of relevant laws, regulations or any terms of the agreement, the user agrees to bear all liability for damages caused thereby.
6. Within the scope permitted by law, this software reserves the right to interpret any terms of this agreement and the right to change it at any time." left="35"  top="0" width="545" height="288" xAlignment="left" yAlignment="top" color="255,255,255" bigfont="0" viewport="1"/>
</window>
